wortys.com 2018-04-01

# Privacy Policy

## Website Privacy Policy

Dalia International

14 Benkovski Street,   
Sofia, BG, 1000

The last update to our Privacy Policy was posted on June 5, 2016. This document governs the privacy policy of our Website, [www.wortys.com](http://www.wortys.com/) – Any capitalized terms not defined herein will have the same meaning as where they are defined elsewhere on our Website.

## _Definitions_

“Non-Personal Information” (NPI) is information that is in no way personally identifiable, and that is obtained automatically when you access our Website with a web browser. “Personally Identifiable Information” (PII) is non-public information that is personally identifiable to you and obtained for us to provide you with a product or service. PII may include information such as your name, address, phone number, credit card information, and other related information that you provide to us.

### Our Commitment to Your Privacy

Our Privacy Policy tells you what PII we may collect from you, how we may share your PII, and how you can limit our sharing of your PII. Dalia International and our affiliates respect your privacy and recognize the need for appropriate protection and management of your PII you share with us.

### Links to Other Websites

Our Website may contain links to other websites. You understand that these websites are not under our control and are not subject to our Privacy Policy. These websites will likely have their own privacy policies. We have no responsibility for these websites and provide links to these websites solely for your convenience. You acknowledge that your use and access of these websites are solely at your own risk. It is your responsibility to check the privacy policies of these websites to see how they treat your personal information.

**Information We Collect**

Generally, you control the amount and type of information you provide to us when using our Website. If you register as a Member to use our Website, you must provide PII in order for us to provide you with various features and/or functionality from our Website. As a Member, we collect your PII in the following ways:

#### At Member Registration

When you register for membership, we collect your name and email address {and other information listed}.

#### Premium Features

Our Website may offer premium features for which you must pay to use. If we were to charge you for the use of these premium features, we would need to collect payment source information (like a credit card) to bill you for using such premium features.

### Computer Information Collected

When you use our Website, we automatically collect certain computer information by the interaction of your mobile phone or web browser with our Website. Such information is typically (but not always) considered NPI. We may also collect any of the following:

#### Cookies

Our Website uses “cookies.” A cookie is a small piece of data or text file stored in your computer or mobile device by your web browser. Cookies may contain text that can be read by a web server that delivered the cookie to you. The text contained in the cookie generally consists of a sequence of letters and numbers that uniquely identifies your computer; however, it may contain other information as well. Cookies are useful because they allow a website to recognize a user’s device. We may use cookies to personalize the Content that you see on our Website. Most web browsers can be set to disable the use of cookies. However, if you disable cookies, you may not be able to access features on our Website correctly or at all.

__Types of Cookies Used__

**Strictly necessary cookies  
**These cookies enable services you have specifically asked for from a Website. These cookies are needed to allow you to navigate around a website and use its features. Without these cookies, services you have requested, like using shopping carts or billing services, cannot be provided.

Examples include:

  * Remembering previous user actions (for example, entered text) when navigating back to a page in the same session.
  * Managing and passing security tokens to different services within a website to identify the visitor’s status (for example, being logged in or not).
  * To preserve tokens for implementing secure areas of a website.

**Performance cookies**

These cookies only collect information about website use for the benefit of our company.

Examples include:

  * _Web analytics_ — the data collected is limited to our use only, for managing the design and performance of our site.
  * _Ad response rates_ — the data is used only for calculating response rates (click-through rates) to improve the effectiveness of advertising bought on a site external to the destination website.
  * _Affiliate tracking_ — this cookie lets affiliates know when a visitor they referred goes to a partner site. It also tells the affiliate if the visitor makes a purchase of a service or product from the partner site, as well as the details of the service or product bought.
  * _Error management_ — this cookie measures errors on a website, usually this will be to support improvement of services or managing complaints and will normally be linked with a website’s analytics.

**Functionality cookies**

These cookies are website specific and are linked to user choices when using a website.

Examples include:

  * Remembering a user’s settings they have applied to a website such as font size, color, layout and other preferences.
  * Remembering a user’s choices about the use of a website.
  * Detecting if a service has been previously offered on a website, such as offering a download or video on future visits to the same website.
  * Providing information to allow an optional service to function such as a live chat session.
  * Fulfilling a request by the user such as submitting or posting a comment.

**Advertising or targeting cookies**

These cookies collect information about your web-browsing behavior. This includes the sites you visit, pages you visit, your time spent on a website and links you click on. These actions create a profile about your web-browsing behavior that links to your web browser. Your profile lets advertisers and publishers show you advertising that is more relevant to your interests.

By agreeing to accept our use of cookies, you are giving us permission to place some or all the cookies described below on your device.  
**We may use cookies for:**

  * Identifying the Areas of Our Website That You Have Visited
  * Signing in and Identifying You as a Member or User to Our Website
  * Our Website Analytics
  * Remarketing Our Products or Services to You
  * Navigating Our Website
  * Remembering Your Preferences and Settings
  * Targeted Advertising
  * Affiliate Marketing

For more information about cookies, visit [www.AboutCookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/).

#### Remarketing Advertising

Why am I seeing ads by for products I’ve viewed?  
Our website uses a remarketing advertising service. Our remarketing service is provided by Facebook. With remarketing, you may see ads for our products you have previously looked at when you use Facebook. For this to happen, Facebook uses a Custom Audience Pixel that is activated when a visitor lands on a web page and a unique “cookie” is placed in their browser.

#### Google Ad and Content Network Privacy Policy

Third-party vendors may include but are not limited to Google, Netseer, Underdogmedia, Content.ad, Revcontent, Taboola, Outbrain, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to our website. Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and/or other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie and other interest-based advertising by visiting:  
If you are in the U.S. – [http://www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/)

If you are in the U.K. – <http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/your-ad-choices>  
If you are in the Canada – <http://youradchoices.ca/choices>

#### Google Analytics Privacy Policy

Our website uses “Google Analytics” to collect information about the use of our site. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit our site, what pages they visit when they do so, and what other sites they used prior to coming to our site. We use the information we get from Google Analytics to improve our site. Google Analytics collects only the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit our site, rather than your name or other identifying information. We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with personally identifiable information. Although Google Analytics plants a permanent cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit our site, the cookie cannot be used by anyone but Google. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to our site is restricted by the Google Analytics Terms of Use. <http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html>

You can prevent Google Analytics from recognizing you on return visits to this site by [disabling cookies](http://www.usa.gov/optout_instructions.shtml) on your browser. <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>

#### Web Beacons

We may also use a technology called “web beacons” (also known as a pixel tag or clear gif) that is delivered through a web browser and certain email client applications to an end user’s computer. The web beacon runs a tag that records a user’s visit to a particular web page.

Web beacons are often used with a web cookie and provided as part of a third-party tracking service. Web beacons along with web server logs allow us to create specific user profiles about their behavior. The information we collect by web beacons also allows us to statistically record the number of people that open our emails.

_Some examples of web beacon use are:_

  * Reporting which emails are read by recipients
  * Recording file downloads
  * Ad campaign management

#### Automatic Information

We automatically receive information from your web browser or mobile device. This information includes the name of the website from which you entered our Website, if any, as well as the name of the website to which you’re headed when you leave our Website. This information also includes the IP address of your computer/proxy server that you use to access the Internet, your Internet website provider name, web browser type, type of mobile device, and computer operating system. We use all of this information to analyze trends among our Users to help improve our Website.

### How Information is Used

We use the information we receive from you as follows:

#### Providing and Improving Our Website

We may use the PII you provide to us along with any computer information we receive to provide our Website to you as well as to make improvements to it.

#### Communications and Email Alerts

When we communicate with you about our Website, we will use the email address you provided when registering as a Member. We may also send you alerts regarding your use of our Website. Finally, we may also send you emails with promotional information about our Website or offers from us or our affiliates, unless you have opted out of receiving such information. You can change contact preferences at any time through your account.

#### Sharing Information with Affiliates and Other Third Parties

We do not sell, rent, or otherwise provide your PII to third parties for marketing purposes. However, we may use your Non Personal Information for data aggregation purposes which might be sold to other parties at our discretion. Any such data aggregation would not contain any of your PII. We may provide your PII to affiliates that provide services with regards to our Website (like payment processors, webhosting companies, etc.)

#### Community Discussion Boards

Our Website may offer the capability for Users to communicate with each other through online Community Discussion Boards. We do not filter or monitor what is posted on such discussion boards. If you chose to post on these discussion boards, you should use care when exposing any PII as such information is not protected by our Privacy Policy nor are we liable should you choose to disclose your PII through such postings.

#### Legally Required Releases of Information

We may be legally required to disclose your PII, if such disclosure is (a) required by subpoena, law, or other legal process; (b) necessary to assist law enforcement officials or government enforcement agencies; (c) necessary to investigate violations of or otherwise enforce our Legal Terms; (d) necessary to protect us from legal action or claims from third parties, including you and/or other Members; and/or (e) necessary to protect the legal rights, personal/real property, or personal safety of our company, our Users, employees, and affiliates.

#### Disclosures to Successors

If our business is sold or merges, in whole or in part, with another business that would become responsible for providing the Website to you, we retain the right to transfer your PII to the new business. The new business would retain the right to use your PII according to the terms of this Privacy Policy as well as to any changes to this Privacy Policy as instituted by the new business.

### Protecting the Privacy Rights of Third Parties

We believe in everyone’s right to privacy. If any postings you make to our Website contain information about third parties, you need to make sure you have permission to include them in your posting. While we are not legally liable for the actions of our Users, we will remove any postings for which we are notified that such postings violate the privacy rights of others.

### Changing Your Information

You may change your PII at any time using facilities found on our Website. If you need assistance with updating your PII or removing yourself from our mailing lists, just send us an email with your request or contact us using our contact information found on our Website.

### Opting Out of Sharing Information

You can always opt out of future unaffiliated third-party disclosures of your information. Such opt-out will not affect disclosures otherwise permitted by law including but not limited to: (i) disclosures to affiliates, (ii) disclosures to third-party service providers who provide certain services for our business, such as credit card processing, computer system services, shipping, data management, or promotional services, (iii) disclosures to third parties as necessary to fulfill your requests, (iv) disclosures to governmental agencies or law enforcement departments or otherwise required to be made under applicable law, (v) previously completed disclosures to third parties, or (vi) disclosures to third parties in connection with subsequent contests or promotions you may choose to enter, or third-party offers you may choose to accept.

### “Do Not Track” Settings

Some web browsers have settings that enable you to request that our Website does not track your movement within our Website. Our Website does not obey such settings when transmitted to and detected by our Website.

**Change and turn off tracking features in your browser.** You can turn off tracking features and other security settings in your browser by visiting the following links:

For Internet Explorer visit: <http://goo.gl/0taI7I>

For Mozilla Firefox visit: <http://goo.gl/IKxt9l>

For Google Chrome visit: <http://goo.gl/NQIkqE>

For Safari visit: <http://goo.gl/7XCOzL>

### Protecting Your Child’s Privacy

We follow the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). Even though our Website is not designed for use by anyone under the age of 18 (child), we realize that a child may attempt to access our Website. We do not knowingly collect PII from a child under the age of 18. If you are a parent or guardian and believe your child is using our Website, please contact us. We may ask for proof of identification before we remove any information to prevent malicious removal of account information. If we discover on our own that a child is accessing our Website, we will delete the information as soon as we discover it, we will not use the information for any purpose, and we will not disclose the information to third parties. You acknowledge that we do not verify the age of our users nor do we have any liability to do so. If you are a child, please seek the permission from a parent or guardian before using our Website.

### Our Email Policy

We comply with the federal CAN-SPAM Act. You can always opt out of receipt of further email correspondence from us or our affiliates. We will not sell, rent, or trade your email address to any unaffiliated third-party without your permission except in the sale or transfer of our business.

### Our Security Policy

We have taken steps to build our Website using industry-standard encryption and authentication tools to protect the security of your PII. When we collect your PII through our Website, we will encrypt your PII before it travels over the Internet using industry-standard technology for conducting secure online transactions. We also use technologies such as secure routers and fire walls to protect your PII. Unfortunately, we cannot fully guarantee secure data transmission over the Internet because of its nature.

Once we receive your PII, we have security measures in place to protect against the loss or misuse of your PII, though again, we cannot fully guarantee against such loss or misuse. We strongly urge you to protect any password you may have for our Website and not share it with anyone. You should always log out of our Website when you are done using it, especially if you are sharing a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place.

### Use of Credit Cards

You may have to provide a credit card to buy products and services from our Website. We use third-party billing services and HAVE NO CONTROL over these services. We use our commercially reasonable efforts to make sure that your credit card number is kept STRICTLY CONFIDENTIAL by using only third-party billing services that use industry-standard encryption technology to protect your credit card number from unauthorized use. However, you understand and agree that we are in no way responsible for any misuse of your credit card number.

**_International Data Transfers_**

Information that we collect may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which we operate in order to enable us to use the information in accordance with this policy. Personal information that you publish on our website or submit for publication on our website may be available, via the Internet, around the world. We cannot prevent the use or misuse of such information by others. You hereby agree to the transfers of personal information described within this section.

### Changes to Our Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to change this privacy policy at any time. If our company decides to change this Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on our website so our users and customers are always aware of what information we collect, use, and disclose. If at any time we decide to disclose or use your PII in a method different from that specified at the time it was collected, we will provide advance notice by email (sent to the email on file in your account). Otherwise, we will use and disclose our users’ and customers’ PII in agreement with the Privacy Policy that was in effect, when their information was collected. In all cases, your continued use of our website or our services and products after any change to this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

### Questions about Our Privacy Policy

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please contact us using our contact information found on our Website.  
This Policy is protected under United States and foreign copyrights. The copying, redistribution, use or publication by you, is strictly prohibited.
